The great outdoors: it’s the place to head for when you’re in need of peace and quiet, open spaces, beautiful scenery and exercise.
户外天地：当你需要内心的宁静、安静开阔的空间、美丽的风景和运动时，这里就是你的目的地。
Whether a huge mountain range or a local country park, these natural areas are a perfect tonic for our stressed-out lives, and their therapeutic effect is being used more and more to treat mental health.
无论是巍峨的山脉，还是本地的郊野公园，这些自然区域都是我们压力重重生活的绝佳良药，它们的治疗效果正越来越多地被用于心理健康治疗。
As an example, in the foothills of the Snowdonia National Park in the UK, specialist therapy sessions are held to help people who suffer from depression, anxiety and stress.
例如，在英国斯诺登尼亚国家公园的山脚下，专门的治疗课程被用于帮助患有抑郁症、焦虑症和承受压力的人群。
Outdoor art-related activities are held for patients, but the setting alone has been credited with improving the mood of patients.
这里为患者举办与艺术相关的户外活动，但仅就环境本身而言，就被认为对改善患者情绪起到了积极作用。
Art psychotherapist Pamela Stanley told the BBC that there was a "growing body of evidence" to support eco-therapy.
艺术心理治疗师帕梅拉·斯坦利向英国广播公司表示，支持生态疗法的“证据越来越多”。
It’s true that for most of us connecting with the natural world definitely lifts our spirits.
诚然，对我们大多数人来说，与自然世界建立联系无疑会振奋精神。
But the mental health charity Mind says eco-therapy has been recognised as a formal type of treatment that can sometimes be prescribed to someone by a doctor.
但心理健康慈善机构“心智”（Mind）表示，生态疗法已被认可为一种正式的治疗方式，医生有时会为患者开具这种治疗方案。
It doesn’t involve taking medication, but instead it just develops a person’s relationship with nature.
它无需服用药物，而是通过培养人与大自然的关系来发挥作用。
This natural remedy can take on many forms, but can include doing yoga in a forest, gardening or even hugging a tree.
这种自然疗法可以有多种形式，包括在森林里做瑜伽、园艺，甚至是拥抱树木。
Evidence has shown there are many benefits of this ‘green’ therapy, including improving social contact, social and work skills and coping abilities.
有证据表明，这种“绿色”疗法有诸多益处，包括改善社交关系、提升社交和工作技能以及应对能力。
It’s what Dr Rachel Bragg from the University of Essex calls ‘psychological restoration’.
埃塞克斯大学的雷切尔·布拉格博士将其称为“心理修复”。
She told the BBC’s All in the Mind programme that nature-based therapies should be part of a "toolkit" of care for patients.
她在接受英国广播公司《心灵深处》（All in the Mind）节目采访时表示，自然疗法应成为患者护理“工具箱”的一部分。
One reason why getting back to nature is, well, natural, is something called biophilia, a sort of understanding or empathy with the natural world.
回归自然之所以“自然而然”，其中一个原因是一种名为“亲生命性”（biophilia）的特质——一种对自然世界的理解或共情能力。
According to environmental psychologist Birgitta Gatersleben, “the idea that nature reminds us of life, and if we (are) exposed to the natural elements, then our sort of negative feelings get almost immediately replaced with positive emotions.”
环境心理学家比吉塔·盖特斯莱本表示：“自然让我们联想到生命，当我们接触自然元素时，负面情绪几乎会立即被积极情绪所取代。”